#### Contact

Hyderabad 9502857898 (Home) raghavreddy876@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ raghavmanyam (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Marketing
Business Development
Social Media Marketing

### Languages

Telugu (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Kannada (Limited Working)

Certifications

Google My Business Basics

Honors-Awards
KEY INNOVATOR of ZaranTech

# Raghav Reddy

Digital Marketing Manager at The ThickShake Factory | Business Development | Growth Hacker

Hyderabad

# Summary

Experienced Digital Marketing with a demonstrated history of working in the E-learning Industry. Skilled in Business Development, Influencer Marketing, Content Marketing, Google ads and Social media ad campaigns, SEO, SMO etc...

An achievement award from the previous organization: https://youtu.be/fbLclq0ymAw

I'm a certified Digital Marketer from Google in Search, Display, Smart, Video, Shopping Ad Campaigns.

# Experience

TTSF Cloud One Digital Marketing Manager May 2022 - Present (3 months) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Performance Marketing and Lead Generation.

The ThickShake Factory
Digital Marketing Manager
May 2021 - April 2022 (1 year)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Pointers:

- # Google Ads
- # Facebook Ads
- # Off Page-SEO
- # Web Designing (WordPress CMS)
- # CRM Integration and Customization
- # WhatsApp API and Flow
- # Google My Business Optimization (GMB)
- # IVR Calling Setup, Email & SMS Campaigns

Emax Technologies
Digital Marketing Analyst
September 2020 - March 2021 (7 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

- # Email Marketing Campaign Planning and Management
- # Google my business GMB Optimization, Using standard technics.
- # Finding high-volume keywords using Google Trends, Keyword Planner.
- # Managing paid campaigns on Google Adwords Search & Display, Bing, Yahoo, Ad Networks
- # Tracking all the Events likes, Page views. Using Google Tag Manager
- # Writing Content to the website based on the google Ads Approval and Disapproval policy
- # Used to write content to Facebook business website depending on their policy
- # Analyze detailed data including Avg. CPC, Impressions, CTR and Conversions Optimization
- # Website Content optimization based on the requirement. CMS
- # Day to Day checking Google Analytics report, for the traffic sources.
- # End to end CRM Software Customization Implementation
- # Posting relevant articles on LinkedIn and Facebook daily basis.
- # Creating Facebook ads and Remarketing as per the requirements.
- # Implementing WhatsApp Business with Automated.
- # SMS marketing involves sending marketing messages to customers via text messages.
- # Tracking Progress in website traffic, lead generations, and conversions
- # Creating, Compelling Ad copy, using GoogleAd Words editor to make bulk changes, Keyword Match types for higher exact match clicks, adding Negative keywords, Keyword research, etc and optimizing for good performance

#### ZaranTech LLC

Digital Marketing Executive
July 2016 - October 2019 (3 years 4 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

- # CRM and Facebook Report regular basis.
- # ZOHO Mailing and SMS Marketing
- # Editing the HTML creative provided by the client
- # Good in LinkedIn Marketing
- # All Types of LinkedIn Premium Accounts handling Sales Navigator, Recruiter, Business.
- # Email and SMS Follow up using CRM, WhatsApp API, Mix Max.

- # Online media marketing, technologies, and pricing models.
- # Involved in Market Research Secondary Research, Leads Generation,
- # Email Campaign, Data Verification, Validation.
- # Facebook ads campaigns and Influencer marketing
- # WhatsApp Marketing, Using Virtual number, SMS Marketing
- # Building queries to extract the data from the database and applying logical filters.
- # Working with creative resources to develop effective designs for all emails as per client requirements.
- # Performing a Quality check before deployment to deliver zero error email campaigns

ProDigital Marketing Lead Generation Executive November 2014 - July 2016 (1 year 9 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

**Email Creation and Email Marketing** 

## Education

Yogi Vemana University, Kadapa Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2010 - 2013)